# esus Arriaga



Website 🔀



jesuarriaga1@gmail.com 😱 MJ2022 **in** Jesus Arriaga 📙

(+34) 656712691

#### **ABOUT ME**

As a web developer I am always attentive to the planning, organization, and structure of all my projects, relying on my knowledge as a Bachelor of Administration that allows me to have a broader idea of how to achieve my goals; To provide solutions to existing problems, I rely on my computer skills and my other non-technical skills that help me to be more efficient in my work performance. am excited to be part of new projects and new experiences that allow me to grow both professionally and as an individual.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Bussiness Administration**

UDO 2013 - 2017 - Nueva Esparta, Venezuela

# The Web Developer Bootcamp

Udemy 2022 -Tenerife, Spain

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Front End Developer

Upwork April, 2022 - Present · Remote.

## Specialized Fiber Optic Installer

Circet April, 2020 - March, 2022 · - Tenerife, Spain.

## Fiber Optic Installer

Cemesa April, 2019 - March, 2020 · -Tenerife, Spain.

#### LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native.

• **English:** Intermediate.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Structuring, accessibility and HTML5.
- Appearance, dynamism and distribution of information: CSS3, SASS.
- Analysis, architecture and design of interactive web apps using modern features of JavaScript.
- Create blogs, eecomerce and web pages with WordPress
- Knowledge of the Vue.js library
- Version control (Git)
- Google Course on Information Technologies.